<title>Michael With A Creeper</title>
<author>People Against Music Theory, George Salazar</author>
<work>Be More Chill</work>
<l>I am hanging with a <an>creeper
<in>In this case it's not a creepy guy, but the creeper mob from <i>Minecraft.</i><br><img src="https://minecraft.wiki/images/Creeper_JE2_BE1.png" height=200>
</in></an> at the biggest party of the swamp</l>
<l>I could stay right here or disappear, and nobody'd even notice at all</l>
<br>
<l>I'm a enderman with a creeper 'cause my buddy kinda left me alone</l>
<l>But I'd rather fake pee than stand awkwardly, or pretend to check a text on my MinePhone</l>
<br>
<l>Everything felt fine when I was half of a pair</l>
<l>Now through no fault of Minecraft, there's no other half there</l>
<br>
<l>Now I'm just Michael with a creeper, Michael with a creeper, mining diamonds</l>
<l>Forget how long it's been</l>
<l>I'm just Michael with a creeper, Michael with a creeper mining diamonds</l>
<l>No you can't come in!</l>
<l>I'm waiting it out 'til it's time to leave</l>
<l>And picking my nose as I softly pee</l>
<l>I'm just Michael who you don't know, Michael flyin' solo, Michael with a creeper by himself</l>
<br>
<l>I am hiding, but he's out there, just ignoring all our history</l>
<l>Chests get erased, and it'll get replaced, with a newer, cooler version of it</l>
<l>And I hear a drunk girl sing along to Alex through the door, "I wanna craft with somebody!"</l>
<l>And my feelings sink, 'cause it makes me think: now there's no one to make fun of drunk girls with anymore!</l>
<br>
<l>Now it's just Michael with a creeper, Michael with a creeper mining diamonds</l>
<l>I half regret the mushroom soup.</l>
<l>(Yeah!)</l>
<l>Michael with a creeper, Michael with a creeper mining diamonds</l>
<l>As I choke back the tears (mod)</l>
<l>I'll wait as long as I need, 'til my face is dry</l>
<l>Or I'll just blame it on a cactus, or something in my eye!</l>
<l>I'm just Michael who you don't know, Michael flyin' solo</l>
<l>Michael with a creeper by himself!</l>
<br>
<l>Block, block, block, block</l>
<l>They're gonna start to shout soon</l>
<l>Block, block, block, block</l>
<l>Oh hell yeah, I'll be out soon</l>
<l>Block, block, block, block</l>
<l>It sucks he left me here alone..</l>
<l>Block, block, block, block</l>
<l>Here in this Minecraft PvP zone..</l>
<l>Clang, clang, clang, clang</l>
<l>I feel the TNT blowing up..</l>
<l>Bang, bang, bang, bang</l>
<l>My big mistake was showing up..</l>
<l>Splash, splash, splash, splash</l>
<br>
<l>I throw a bucket in my face</l>
<l>And I am in a better place</l>
<l>I go to open up the door</l>
<l>But I can't hear blocking</l>
<l>Anymore</l>
<br>
<l>And I can't help but mine</l>
<l>For a different mine</l>
<l>And then I look in the glass</l>
<l>And the present is clearer</l>
<l>And there's no denying, I'm just..</l>
<br>
<l>Mining diamonds</l>
<l>Is there a sadder sight than...</l>
<l>Michael with a creeper mining diamonds</l>
<l>This is a heinous night <an>(Don't mine at night)<in>A reference to "Don't Mine At Night" by Bebop Vox, but erroneously sung to the tune of "Take Back The Night" bu Justin Timberlake.</in></an></l>
<l>I wish I stayed at home in bed watching Minecraft porn</l>
<l>Or wish I <an>[silence]<in>We don't joke about suicide.</in></an></l>
<l>I'm just Michael who's a loner</l>
<l>He's such a fucking b[bleep]</l>
<l>Rides a worn elytra</l>
<l>God he's such a pooper</l>
<l>Michael flyin' solo</l>
<l>Who you think that you know</l>
<l>Michael with a creeper by himself</l>
<l>All by himself</l>
<l>All by himself</l>
<l>All you know about me is my username</l>
<l>Awesome party</l>
<l>I'm so glad I came</l>